So I just want to lay something out. So let's say there's this group of voters
that believe in their stuff. And there's this group of voters that believe in their stuff.
And here's the candidate. And the candidate needs both groups in order to win. However,
the candidate says, I'm only thinking about this group. I don't care about this group.
But what happens is that that candidate is no longer viable to win because he has left this
group out. So this group has to make a decision. We could still be loyal to this candidate,
even though it's not going to get us anywhere. And it makes us look like we don't care about what
our other peoples care about, which makes us just seem like we're not in community with them,
even though we are, whether this candidate wins or not. Or we could create coalition
interest convergence, if you will, with the group that's getting left out and push that candidate
to actually meet both of our needs to give them an actual shot. What happens far too often is that
this group says, if you want us to care, you need to let go of that that you care about,
even though the candidate doesn't care about you. Plot twist. The candidate don't care about none of
y'all. Literally. The candidate only cares about your vote and their ability to win. That's all you're
useful for. You're not working alongside that candidate. You're not living alongside that candidate.
The candidate is working and living alongside these lobbyists and other folks. That's who they care
about. Once you give them your vote, they don't have any other obligation to you that they're going
to stand on. However, the people you're in community with, you all have an obligation to each other.
And those candidates just build distrust between you and the people in your community.
So again, there's you, there's them, and there's that. You have what you're about. They have what
they're about. And then there's that candidate. If that candidate only cares about what some of y'all
are about, then they're only going to get some of your votes. And that means they're not going to win
anything. I'm hoping that this may be in a different picture in your mind. Support a real one.